<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Prestashop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Prestashop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://devdocs.prestashop.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/basics/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/basics/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentals of PrestaShop Development PrestaShop was conceived so that third-party modules could easily build upon its foundations, making it an extremely customizable e-commerce software.
PrestaShop’s customization is based on three possibilities:
 Themes, Modules, Overriding.  Themes are explored in full in the Designer Guide.
Modules and the override system are explored in this Developer Guide, starting with the “Concepts” section below. You can learn more about each in the following chapters:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/basics/installation/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/basics/installation/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuring PrestaShop By default, PrestaShop is configured to provide a secure and stable environment to both the shop administrator and the customers.
As a developer, there are several changes that you could and should bring to the default installation in order to help you code better, spot bugs faster, and generally make a great PrestaShop product.
Disabling the cache and forcing Smarty compilation When your development has an impact on the front office, whether you are building a theme or simply a module which displays information to the customer, you should force the template file compilation and disable the cache, so as to always see the result of your changes directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ObjectModel</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/development/database/objectmodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/development/database/objectmodel/</guid>
      <description>The ObjectModel class When needing to dive deep, you have to use the ObjectModel class. This is the main object of PrestaShop’s object model. It can be overridden… with precaution.
It is an Active Record kind of class (see: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Active_record_pattern). The table attributes or view attributes of PrestaShop’s database are encapsulated in this class. Therefore, the class is tied to a database record. After the object has been instantiated, a new record is added to the database.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>